increase.academy 2018-08-13

# Privacy Policy – SeanVosler

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the increase.academy and Vezign LLC and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Vezign LLC include increase.academy, Increase Academy, increase.academy and increase.ventures. The Vezign LLC website is a news and information site. By using the Vezign LLC website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Collection of your Personal Information

Vezign LLC may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Vezign LLC. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Vezign LLC website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Vezign LLC’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

Vezign LLC encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Vezign LLC so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Vezign LLC is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Vezign LLC website.

Use of your Personal Information

Vezign LLC collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Vezign LLC may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Vezign LLC and its affiliates. Vezign LLC may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Vezign LLC does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Vezign LLC may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is transferred to the third party. Vezign LLC may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Vezign LLC, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Vezign LLC may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Vezign LLC, in order to determine what Vezign LLC services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Vezign LLC to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Vezign LLC will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Vezign LLC or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Vezign LLC; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Vezign LLC, or the public.

Use of Cookies

The Vezign LLC website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Vezign LLC pages, or register with Vezign LLC site or services, a cookie helps Vezign LLC to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Vezign LLC website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Vezign LLC features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Vezign LLC services or websites you visit.  
Security of your Personal Information  
Vezign LLC secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.  
Children Under Thirteen  
Vezign LLC does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.  
Disconnecting your Vezign LLC Account from Third Party Websites  
You will be able to connect your Vezign LLC account to third party accounts.

CONNECTING YOUR VEZIGN LLC ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED INTHIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. Users may contact us via email: support@increase.academy.  
Opt-Out & Unsubscribe  
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Vezign LLC by contacting us here:  
– Web page: _________________  
– Email: support@increase.academy – Phone: _________________  
Changes to this Statement  
Vezign LLC will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Vezign LLC encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Vezign LLC is protecting your information.  
Contact Information  
Vezign LLC welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Vezign LLC has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Vezign LLC at:  
Vezign LLC  
4490 Fanuel St, #213  
San Diego, California 92109  
Email Address: support@increase.academy  
Telephone number: 415-483-9446  
Effective as of December 22, 2015
